Contact

951-312-5122 (Mobile) tiffany_boyett@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tiffany-holland-boyett-83b925106 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Critical Care
ICU
Medical-Surgical

Languages

English

Certifications

Public Health Nurse BLS ACLS

AACN member Registered Nurse

Tiffany Holland (Boyett)

Cardiovascular ICU RN, CCRN, BSN, PHN United States

Summary

I am a hard working, compassionate, and driven Critical Care Nurse who delivers safe and efficient care to a variety of adult patient populations. I am a trained open heart recovery nurse and certified in IABP, Impella pump, CRRT, and post interventional cardiac catheterization patients. I am experienced and skilled in Neuro and Medical Surgical Critical Care and am certified in NIH Stroke Scale. I believe in serving as a patient advocate and part of a multi disciplinary team to provide the best care possible to my patients. I am a designated preceptor and Relief Charge Nurse and am skilled in Cerner, Epic, and computer charting.

Experience

Kaiser Permanente
CVICU Registered Nurse
February 2017 - Present (3 years 5 months)
Fontana, California

Trained in immediate open heart recovery, CABG, Valve replacements, TAVR, IABP, post cardiac cath/intervention, and also skilled in over flow medical/ surgical ICU patients.

Temecula Valley Hospital Critical Care Registered Nurse, Relief Charge Nurse, Preceptor November 2013 - February 2017 (3 years 4 months)

Temecula, California

Stroke and STEMI certified, Cardio Thoracic/Cardiac, Neuro, Medical-Surgical ICU, Relief Charge Nurse, Preceptor

Loma Linda University Medical Center Murrieta Critical Care RN, Relief Charge Nurse, Preceptor December 2011 - October 2013 (1 year 11 months) Murrieta, California

Medical Surgical, Cardio Thoracic/ Cardiac Cath, Neuro ICU, STEMI

Loma Linda University Medical Center Critical Care RN July 2009 - December 2011 (2 years 6 months) Loma Linda, California

Medical ICU

Mercy Hospital of Bakersfield Nurse Extern September 2008 - June 2009 (10 months) Bakersfield, California

Nursing Student Extern in ICU and ER.

Education

California State University-Bakersfield
BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2006 - 2009)

Humboldt State University undergraduate, nursing pre requisites, Pre-Nursing Studies · (2004 - 2006)

Murrieta Valley High School
Diploma, General Education · (2000 - 2004)